Guide to the Robert G. Dixon, Jr. Records 1942-1944
Dixon, Jr., Robert G. Records
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Robert G. Dixon, Jr. Records, 1942-1944
5442
Dixon, Robert G., Jr.
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Decisions, reports, and related documents of the National War Labor Board, dating from 1942 to 1945.
1 cubic feet
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Richard G. Dixon was Professor of Law at Georgetown University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection consists of decisions, reports, and related documents of the National War Labor Board. Dating from 1942 to 1945, these materials were collected by Professor Richard G. Dixon of the Georgetown University Law School.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Dixon, Robert Galloway, 1920-; United States. National War Labor Board (1918-1919)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Decisions, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Decisions, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Marked for special reference, double and triple checked
- General orders, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Folder 1 of 3
- Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Folder 2 of 3
- Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Folder 3 of 3